Bedau, Hugo A.; Papers apap199
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1957-2003; Undated; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  - Individual, 1963-1991; Undated; 2.1
    - Barend v.d. van Niekerk, 1973-1977 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - David Pannick, 1981-1985 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Peter Passell, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Michael Radelet, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Marc Riedel, 1973-1977 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Austin Sarat/Neil Vidmar, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Karl Schuessler, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
    - Jack Schwartz, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Henry Schwarzchild, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8A)
    - George Solomon, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - Sheila Spaulding, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - Jan Stephan, 1974-1988 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
    - Murray Straus, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - Victor Streib, 1985-1988 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - Charles Thomas, 1973-1982 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - Charles Thomas/Samuel Foster, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - Neil Vidmar, 1972-1977 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - Louis West, 1973-1975 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Burton Wides, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
    - Welsh White, 1973-1975 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
    - James Wilson, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Edwin Wolf, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
    - Marvin Wolfgang/Marc Riedel, 1972-1979 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22-23)
    - Wendy Wolfson, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
    - Martin Yant/Plagiarism Case, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
    - Hans Zeisel, 1976-1988 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
    - Franklyn Zimring, 1973-1976 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Chronological, 1957-2002; 2.2
    This subseries contains routine and general correspondence organized chronologically by year.
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29-30)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31-33)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Subject, 1959-2003; 2.3
    This subseries contains Bedau's correspondence with publishers and researchers regarding some of his publications. It is organized alphabetically by title of publication. The final section in this series concerns the Harold Otey case. Bedau was a strong advocate for freeing Otey. The correspondence includes letters to and from Nebraska's governor, Otey's lawyer, and Otey himself. Also included are academic works, a transcript of his commutation hearing and appeals and newspaper articles.
    Folders contain correspondence with publishers, researchers, etc.
    - Capital Punishment in the United States, 1976 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
      Edited and Introduction by Hugo Bedau and Chester M. Pierce (See also: Capital Punishment issue of American Journal of Othopsychiatry, 1975).
    - Capital Punishment in the United States, 1977-1983 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - The Courts, the Constitution, and Capital Punishment, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - The Courts, the Constitution, and Capital Punishment, 1975-1988 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Death Penalty in America, 1959-1967 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18-21)
    - Death Penalty in America, 1967-1971 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
      For 1971 revision.
    - Death Penalty in America, 1972-1978 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
    - Death Penalty in America (1979 revision) (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Death Penalty in America, 1980-1991 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2-3)
    - Death Penalty in America: Current Controversies, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4-6)
    - Death is Different, 1985-1987 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
    - Death is Different, 1987 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Debating the Death Penalty, 2003, 2001-2003 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - In Spite of Innocence, 1992 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10-11)
    - In Spite of Innocence, 1992 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - In Spite of Innocence, 1993 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - In Spite of Innocence 2nd Edition, 2002 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - Killing as Punishment: Reflections on the Death Penalty in America, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15-16)
    - Harold Otey Case, Appeals for Clemency, 1995 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Harold Otey Case, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18-19)
    - "How Evidence Supports the Issues in Commutation Hearing of Harold Otey", 1991 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Nebraska Board of Pardons meeting concerning Harold Otey transcript, 1991 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
    - Harold Otey Case, 1993 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
    - Poetry of Harold Otey, 1985-1991 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
- Advocacy Organization, 1958-2003; 3; 10 cubic ft.
  This series contains a diverse collection of material regarding Bedau's participation in many advocacy organizations opposing capital punishment. These organizations include: the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), Massachusetts Citizens Against the Death Penalty (MCADP), Amnesty International, American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), and the Legal Defense Fund (LDF). Since Bedau was on the Board of many of these organizations, the folders contain the minutes of meetings, projects, events, and conferences.
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), 1981-2001; 3.1
    This subseries contains chronologically arranged materials related to the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty including copies of the NCADP newsletter Lifelines, from 1981-1999.
    - NCADP, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 1)
    - NCADP, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 2)
    - NCADP, Legislative Handbook, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 3)
    - NCADP, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 4)
    - NCADP, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 5)
    - NCADP, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 6)
    - NCADP, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 7-8)
    - NCADP, Conference, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 9)
    - NCADP, Survey of State Legislation, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 10)
    - NCADP, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 11-12)
    - NCADP, Conference, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 13)
    - NCADP, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 14-15)
    - NCADP, National Perspectives Portfolio, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 16)
    - NCADP, "Stop It" Campaign, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 17)
    - NCADP, Survey of State Legislation, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 18)
    - NCADP, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19-21)
    - NCADP, Informational Bibliography on the Death Penalty, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 22)
    - NCADP, Survey of State Legislation, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 23)
    - NCADP, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 24)
    - NCADP, Annual Report, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 25)
    - NCADP, Survey of State Legislation, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 26)
    - NCADP, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 27-28)
    - NCADP, Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 29)
    - NCADP, Brennan Project, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 30)
    - NCADP, Board Meeting. Development Report, 1995 November 11-12 (Box 1 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 31)
    - NCADP, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 1)
    - NCADP, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 2)
    - NCADP, Annual Conference, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 3)
    - NCADP, 20th Anniversary Conference, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 4)
    - NCADP, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 5)
    - NCADP, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 6)
    - NCADP, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 7)
    - NCADP, Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 8)
    - NCADP, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 9-10)
    - NCADP, Annual Conference, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 11)
    - NCADP, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 12)
    - NCADP, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 13)
    - NCADP, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 14)
    - NCADP, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 15)
    - NCADP, Board of Directors, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 16)
    - NCADP, First Quarter Development Report, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 17)
    - NCADP, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 18)
    - NCADP, 2001 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19)
    - NCADP, Annual Conference, 2001 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 20)
    - NCADP, Abolitionist Directory, 2001 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 21)
    - NCADP Lifelines, 1981-May 1985 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 22)
    - NCADP Lifelines, 1985 June-1988 August (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 23)
    - NCADP Lifelines, 1988 September-1992 December (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 24)
    - NCADP Lifelines, 1993 January-1998 December (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 25)
    - NCADP Lifelines, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 26)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Against the Death Penalty (MCADP), 1968-1998; 3.2
    This subseries contains chronologically arranged materials related to the MCADP.
    - MCADP, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 1-2)
    - MCARDP, 1981 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 3)
    - MCARDP, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 4-5)
    - MCARDP, Referendum, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 6)
    - MCARDP, Resource Packet, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 7)
    - MCARDP/MCADP, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 8)
    - MCADP, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 9)
    - MCADP, 1985 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 10)
    - MCADP, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 11)
    - MCADP, 1988 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 12)
    - MCADP, 1989 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 13)
    - MCADP, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 14-15)
    - MCADP, Speaker's Bureau, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 16)
    - MCADP, Speaker's Packet, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 17-18)
    - MCADP, 1991 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19)
    - MCADP, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 20-21)
    - MCADP, Resource Packet, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 22)
    - MCADP, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 23)
    - MCADP, 1995 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 24)
    - MCADP, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 25)
    - MCADP, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 26)
  - Legal Defense Fund (LDF), 1970-2003; 3.3
    This subseries contains chronologically arranged materials related to the Legal Defense Fund, including the newsletter, Death Row UNITED STATES.
    - LDF Equal Justice Newsletter, 1970 June-1970 July (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 1)
    - LDF, Conference, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 2)
    - LDF Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 3)
    - LDF, Research on change from mandatory to Discretionary Capital Punishment Statutes, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 4)
    - LDF, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 5)
    - LDF, Empirical Propositions in Furman, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 6)
    - LDF, 1984-1990 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 7)
    - Death Row United States, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 8)
    - Death Row United States, 1976-1977 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 9)
    - Death Row United States, 1980 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 10)
    - Death Row United States, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 11)
    - Death Row United States, 1982 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 12)
    - Death Row United States, 1983 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 13)
    - Death Row United States, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 14)
    - Death Row United States, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 15)
    - Death Row United States, 1986 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 16)
    - Death Row United States, 1987 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 17)
    - Death Row United States, 1988 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 18)
    - Death Row United States, 1989-1991 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19)
    - Death Row United States, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 20)
    - Death Row United States, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 21)
    - Death Row United States, 1995-1997 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 22)
    - Death Row United States, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 23)
    - Death Row United States, 2000-2001 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 24)
    - Death Row United States, 2002-2003 (Box 4 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 25)
  - State Public Defenders/ California Appellate Project (CAP), 1982-2002; 3.4
    Defenders/California Appellate Project (CAP). It was originally entitled the Death Penalty Update but its name was changed to the RECAP Newsletter in 1984. Also in this subseries are four copies of the Death Penalty Information Bank published in 1983, 1984, 2000-2001, and 2002-2003.
    - Death Penalty Update, 1982 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 1)
    - Death Penalty Update, 1983 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 2-3)
    - Death Penalty Update, 1984 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 4)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 5-6)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 7)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1989 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 8)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1990 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 9)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1994 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 10)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1995 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 11)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1996 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 12)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1997 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 13-14)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 1999 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 15)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 2000 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 16-17)
    - RECAP Newsletter, 2001 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 18)
    - Death Penalty Information Bank, 1983 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19)
    - Death Penalty Information Bank, 1984 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 20)
    - Death Penalty Information Bank, 1998 (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 21)
    - Death Penalty Information Bank, 2000; CD-ROM (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 22)
    - Death Penalty Index, 2002; CD-ROM (Box 5 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations, 1957-2002; Undated; 3.5
    This subseries contains alphabetically arranged materials related to various advocacy groups including Amnesty International and the American Civil Liberties Union. There are also folders labeled "Various Organizations" which contains materials from many organizations including: the Alabama Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty, Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation, Detention Ministry and the Colorado Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty.
    - Advocacy Organization Buttons, Undated (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 1)
    - American Bar Association, "Resolution to Oppose the Death Penalty Internationally", 1987 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 2)
    - American Bar Association, 1997 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 3)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), Community Action Manual, 1968 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 4)
    - ACLU, Correspondence, 1973-1991 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 5)
    - ACLU, Deathwatch Newsletter, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 6)
    - ACLU, 1983-1989 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 7)
    - ACLU, the Case Against S.239, 1986 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 8)
    - ACLU, Abolitionist Newsletter, 1997-2001 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 9)
    - American Correctional Association, 1957 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 10)
    - American Indians and the Death Penalty, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 11)
    - American League to Abolish Capital Punishment (ALACP), 1960-1969 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 12)
    - ALACP, 1970-1971 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 13)
    - ALACP, Financial Records, 1972-1976 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 14)
    - American Philosophical Society, 2002 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 15)
    - Americans for Effective Law Enforcement, 1973 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 16)
    - American Society of Criminology, 1988-1991 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 17)
    - Amnesty International, Handbook, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 18)
    - Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolition of the Death Penalty, Stockholm, 1977; 3.5.19 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19-21)
      - Amnesty International, 1978-1980 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 22-23)
      - Amnesty International, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 24)
      - Amnesty International, 1983-1986 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 25)
      - Amnesty International, Death Penalty Log, 1983-1986 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 26)
      - Amnesty International, 1987-1989 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 27)
      - Amnesty International, Death Penalty News, 1988-1989 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 28)
      - Amnesty International, 1990-1998 (Box 6 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 29)
      - Amnesty International, Death Penalty and Political Campaigns, 1992 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 1)
      - Amnesty International United States, Death Penalty Mailing, 1994 February-December (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 2)
      - Amnesty International United States, Death Penalty Mailing, 1995 January-June (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 3)
      - Andrew Lee Jones Fund -- Assisting Lawyers for Justice on Death Row, 1996 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 4)
      - Bruderhof Foundation, 1996 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 5)
      - Bureau of Prisons, 1961 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 6)
      - Citizens Against Legalized Murder (CALM), Death Row Census, 1971-1972 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 7)
      - CALM, Newsletter, 1971-1972 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 8)
      - Capital Report, Newsletter of National Legal Aid and Defender Association (NLADA), 1987 September-1991 November (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 9)
      - Capital Report, NLADA, Capital Report Index 2nd Edition, 1991 November-1994 December (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 10)
      - Capital Report, NLADA, 1995 March-1998 April (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 11)
      - Catholics Against Capital Punishment (CACP), 1980-2000 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 12)
      - CACP News Notes, 1996-2005 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 13)
      - Center for Responsive Psychology, 1977 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 14)
      - Centurion Ministries, 1996-2004 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 15)
      - Citizens United for Alternative to the Death Penalty, 1997 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 16)
      - Coalition to Keep Kansas Free of the Death Penalty, 1986 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 17)
      - Colorado Coalition Against the Death Penalty Newsletter, 1985-1989 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 18)
      - Committee for a "No" Vote on Question #6, 1968 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 19-20)
      - Congressional Digest Corporation, 1973 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 21)
      - Death Penalty Documentation Project, New York University Law School, 1998 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 22)
      - Death Penalty Information Center (DPIC), 1990-1991 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 23)
      - DPIC, 1993-2003 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 24)
      - DPIC, Thurgood Marshall Journalism Award, 2002 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 25)